bloomenergy.com 2011-11-03

# Bloom Energy | Be The Solution | Privacy Policy

**Our Commitment to Your Privacy**  
This site is owned and operated by Bloom Energy. You should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

**The Information We Collect:**  
When you access Bloom Energy's Web site, you provide certain personally identifiable information. Examples of this information may be any of the following: your name, e-mail address, affiliation, personal address, personal phone number, demographic information, contact preferences, and personal and/or professional opinions.

**Online Newsletters**  
When you subscribe to our online newsletters, there are instructions at the bottom of your e-mail newsletter telling you how to unsubscribe if you ever wish to do so.

**Surveys**  
Bloom Energy may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. (We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party.)

**Children**  
Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent. Kids, please, be sure to ask your parents for permission before you send any information about yourself to us or anyone else online or over the Internet.

**Cookies**  
We use cookies on our Web site to help tailor your experience at our Web site. Cookies are little bits of electronic information that a Web site can store on your computer to help personalize your visit to Bloom Energy Web site. The cookie itself does not contain personal information, although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. Bloom Energy uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). Our advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser.
